What are the most important team-ups in human history? Tom Brady with the Patriots, Bose,
and arrows, peanut butter, meeting jelly? What if I told you all of these are Weenie Hut Jr.
level team-ups compared to what I'm about to talk about today? This is something special we've
been cooking up here and I'm excited to be able to show you it, and I hope you're ready to have
your entire world rocked as a result. I was stinky once, then I died. It killed me.
But luckily, an angel was nearby and cracked open a box of cheeky soap and rubbed me down,
brought me back to life for my odors overdose. I can still hear that beautiful voice echoing in my
ears. Charlie say it with me, Charlie. That's right. I knew that the only thing that could say poor
old Charlie from that stank death that he was about to suffer was a beautiful elegant bar of cheeky
soap by far the best soap that I've ever used. Is that a bar of low-fi lavender, Charlie?
That's my favorite. Can I get one? Boy, howdy, is it ever?
Thanks, Charlie. Oh, this is my favorite. Thanks for letting me borrow this, Charlie.
I got some extras for you too. Here you go.
Thanks, soap angel. So if you want to avoid almost dying because of some stank action like
poor old Charlie did, go ahead and make sure you stay clean with cheek. It'll keep their cheeks clean.
Yeah, that's right. Keso is now an owner of cheeky with us. My favorite streamer,
someone I've glazed out the wazoo for a long time now is now someone that I can call a brother,
only closer. We bade together, metaphorically speaking. Keso is someone that we sent soap to,
just on a whim because we all really like his content. And he ended up really liking our soap a lot.
He liked it so much that he wanted to get more involved with cheeky, which we were more than happy
to do. He is the perfect fit for our soap. Dr. Squatch has Sydney Swini, but that shit is small
potato is compared to Keso. That's the real heartthrob right there. And Keso is extremely
passionate about our soap and what we're aiming to do with it. So having him on board and as pumped
as we are about it is just it's a joy. Call me Weddy Kruger, the way I'm infiltrating your dreams
and making them a reality here with this team up, given you a reason to bust in those bridges.
The Keso team up here with cheeky is one for the history books. And I am so excited for the
stuff we're going to do together. Now for those that don't know about cheeky, I've talked about it
quite a bit and I made a whole video kind of explaining the history of how it came into being.
But I'll go ahead and give you like the cliff notes on it. I've already told you the story of
why the soap came into being the genesis of cheeky. In a nutshell, I have psoriasis and after showers
for the longest time I'd always feel really dry. I eventually switched the bar soap and it helped,
but I thought it could be better. So we spent a couple years theory crafting and working towards
the perfect bar of soap that would be very moisturizing for me in my condition. And we found it.
In search of perfection we succeeded. We created a all natural bar soap that works extremely well
for my skin and is highly moisturizing. So even if you don't have like psoriasis or anything,
it's just a really good bar of soap that will leave you feeling really refreshed afterwards.
It has all natural ingredients like I said, but also moisturizing elements to it as well,
like a hobo oil shed butter that kind of thing. We literally made it just for me to solve a problem,
well not solve a problem. Like it doesn't cure psoriasis or anything like that, but it makes me feel
significantly better after showers. So no longer feel like fucking sponge Bob when he goes into
sandy cheeks dumb without us helmet on. Like it, it has helped me and that was the purpose of it.
But when we started giving it to like friends and family, they really liked it and then eventually
we decided we'll just go ahead and let other people try it as well. So we started sowing it about
nine months ago last November. Oh actually almost a year ago now and people have really responded
very well to it, which I'm super happy about. And I don't want people to just take my word for it.
And I know a lot of people can just write off testimonials as being you know page chills or
it could just be people that like Charlie so they'll just say anything nice about the product.
And I understand because rightfully so the youtuber product space is a complete cesspool. It is
hard to trust claims like that. So I want you to have the cold hard facts, the brass tacks.
So we sent cheeky to a laboratory, an independent lab to thoroughly test our moisturizing claims.
And they spent a few months going through the ringer. And we now have the report to confirm that our
soap is moisturizing. It does do what we claim. It has been signed off by dermatologist as well,
the study. And I want people to have access to that. So I thought it would be fun to have cheeky
be like fully open with like everything that comes with soap and soap making and everything like
hygiene related. So we're going to be putting a section on cheeky use cheeky.com where you can
see all of the studies that we're going to be running on cheeky. This is just the first of many.
We want to have as much science and research done on it as possible so people could have all of
this information at their fingertips as well as having our chemist explain why certain things are
there, how it works. And just like this really detailed breakdown of everything that goes into it.
Because I think the more information you have, the better. So right now in the site, we have this
section here that goes over the clinical study. Now it's not the full 48 pages yet. Right now we're
still going through and redacting some private information like addresses and such. But we have like
the key takeaways from the clinical outcome here. And we will be posting the full 48 pages for
anyone that wants to go through and take the dive and learn everything about what was tested in how.
Again, we're all super pumped to have KSO on board and the stuff that we're going to do together
is going to be fucking incredible. And we have more big cheeky news around the corner as well.
I don't think I'm allowed to like go too deep into detail on it. But I can at least tell you like
one of the things we have a lot of really big anime collabs in the works right now as partnerships
with cheeky. It's all just extremely exciting. So again, hopefully you're as excited as we are.
I want to give you some bloopers here from the hot tub filming.
The whole thing you're saying you think I can still hear light opens up. What is he said?
He's he goes in there and he says, yeah, oh, he made me say it. It'd be me. The soap range.
Honestly, I don't think I'm doing something with soap toss. Yeah, do the soap toss. I feel like
you if someone if cinema sins is going to digest our storyline, there's going to be holes in it. But I think it'll be fine.
Cheeky available in tons of wonderful sense, all of which very moisturizing will make you feel great after
a shower. Hygiene is very important. People will hate you if you don't smell good. They might
already hate you, but smelling good will definitely be one thing they can't hate you for.
They're the fucking bastard you. I'm not afraid to show how natural I am. Check out this cellulator,
cellulator my balls. No, come in close with tea bagging.
And you just stand up, no, no, no. Oh yeah, then you just stand up.
I'm going to be fine for everyone like you're ever seen a 30 year old man take a bath.
You have now and he's happy because he's using cheeky.
You're not going to believe this. I saw a soap that wasn't cheeky once.
Can't believe I made it out of that store without beating someone's.
My favorite is if you put this all together for a video. It's just three men and a bad one.
Talking to you at a bathtub. Damn right. Go to use cheeky.com and get some of the best soap in
the universe packed with moisturizing ingredients all natural. Have you feeling great after a shower?
Yes, here about that dude that fell asleep in the bathtub. He fucking went into this clean,
cleanliness dimension. All he saw was cheeky.
Use cheeky.com has some wonderful sense like low-fi lavender and of course the iconic pulp,
Francis gone but not forgotten and mortalized forever in cheeky soap.
Oh, I got some top down. Wait, check this. Everyone shut up. Watch this.
Oh my god.
Go to use cheeky.com.
Oh, you're so nice. Sydney Swini doesn't want you to see this.
You best start believing in soap stories.
There, I've got another idea. I can just make more in the tub. That's true.
There's still something on the gill. There's still something on the gill.
Yeah, there is.
I'm recording this process about making bubble.
This is probably how real productions make their bubble stop.
These terms for splashes and bubbleists working pretty good.
It does work.
You think this is what they did in Sydney Swini?
It puts you in the tub.
Sydney getting the, but all the crew come to this.